Bill Pelke Papers
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Amnesty International, 1988-2000, Undated; nam_apap205-4; 3.75 cubic feet
  - On the Internet, Undated; nam_apap205-4_176 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Open Letter to the President on the Death Penalty, 1994; nam_apap205-4_177 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Packet, 1989; nam_apap205-4_178 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Personal Courage and Conscience, 1991; nam_apap205-4_179 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Philippines: The Death Penalty, 1997; nam_apap205-4_180 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Policy and Guidelines on Cooperative Activities Between Amnesty International and the Human Rights Movement, 1996; nam_apap205-4_181 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Poster Draft, circa 1991; nam_apap205-4_182 (Oversize 8, Folder 3)
  - Preventing the Imposition of the Death Penalty, Undated; nam_apap205-4_183 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Protection of Persons, 1992; nam_apap205-4_184 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Public Identification with AI and Cooperation with Outside Groups, 1992; nam_apap205-4_185 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Publications Catalogue, 1995; 1998-1999; nam_apap205-4_186 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Questionnaire for Mission Delegates, 1996; nam_apap205-4_187 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Ratification Now!, Undated; nam_apap205-4_188 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Refugee Issues World Conference on Human Rights, 1993; nam_apap205-4_189 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Readings for Human Rights, 1990; nam_apap205-4_190 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Relief Policies and Procedures, Undated; nam_apap205-4_191 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Religious Action, 1993; 1992; nam_apap205-4_192 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Report of Local Group Activity, 1992; nam_apap205-4_193 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Report of Death Penalty Legislation in the United States of America, 1996; nam_apap205-4_194 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Rights for All, 1998; nam_apap205-4_195 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Scaling the Wall, Undated; nam_apap205-4_196 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Speakers List, 1995; nam_apap205-4_197 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Special Initiatives Fund, 1996; nam_apap205-4_198 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - State Death Penalty Action Coordinators Folder, 1994-1995; nam_apap205-4_199 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - State Death Penalty Abolition Coordinators, Undated; nam_apap205-4_200 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Statements for the Mumia Abu - Jamal Speak Out, 1994; nam_apap205-4_201 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Statute of Amnesty International, 1995; nam_apap205-4_202 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Stickers and Bumpber Stickers, Undated; nam_apap205-4_203 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Summer Postcard Action, 1993; 1996-1998; nam_apap205-4_204 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Taiwan - Ill - Treatment in Death Row, 1993; nam_apap205-4_205 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Texas and the USA, 1997; nam_apap205-4_206 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Tip of the Month, Undated; nam_apap205-4_207 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Trainer Address and Phone List, Undated; nam_apap205-4_208 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Trainer's Handbook, 1991; nam_apap205-4_209 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Training of Trainers Program, 1993; nam_apap205-4_210 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - The Truth about the Death Penalty in the United States in Real News, 1990; nam_apap205-4_211 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Upcoming Anti - Death Penalty Action, 1994; nam_apap205-4_212 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Urgent Action Appeal, 1990; nam_apap205-4_213 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Urgent Action Appeal, 1991; nam_apap205-4_214 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Urgent Action Appeal, 1992; nam_apap205-4_215 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Urgent Action Appeal, 1993; nam_apap205-4_216 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Urgent Action Appeal, 1994; nam_apap205-4_217 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Urgent Action Appeal, 1995; nam_apap205-4_218 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Urgent Action Appeal, 1997; nam_apap205-4_219 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Urgent Action Network Survey, 1995; nam_apap205-4_220 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Urgent Action Newsletter, 1994; nam_apap205-4_221 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Urgent Action Newsletter, 1995; nam_apap205-4_222 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Urgent Action Newsletter, 1995; nam_apap205-4_223 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Urgent Action Telegram Pledge Program, 1991; nam_apap205-4_224 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - USA The Death Penalty and Juvenile Offenders, 1991; nam_apap205-4_225 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - USA The Death Penalty Briefing, 1987; nam_apap205-4_226 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Voices, 1993; nam_apap205-4_227 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Voices for Freedom, Undated; nam_apap205-4_228 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Voter Involvement Form, 1993; 1996-1997; nam_apap205-4_229 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Western Region Human Rights Education Institute, 1997; nam_apap205-4_230 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Western Regional Conference, 1992; Undated; nam_apap205-4_231 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - When the State Kills, 1989; nam_apap205-4_232 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Who's Who, 1995; nam_apap205-4_233 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Women's Day Action, 1994; nam_apap205-4_234 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Women's Day Activists, 1997; nam_apap205-4_235 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - World Conference Vol I, 1993; nam_apap205-4_236 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - World Conference Vol II, 1993; nam_apap205-4_237 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1988-1999, Undated; nam_apap205-5; 1.23 cubic feet
  This series documents Bill Pelkes involvement in National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (NCADP). Items included in this series include documents related to Bill Pelkes role as a board member, newsletters, conference documents, flyers, pamphlets, and other outreach materials collected by Bill Pelke.
  - The Abolotionist's Directory, 1992-1995; nam_apap205-5_1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Abolotionist's Directory, 1997-1998; nam_apap205-5_2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Administrative, 1989; nam_apap205-5_3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Administrative, 1990; nam_apap205-5_4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Administrative, 1991; nam_apap205-5_5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Administrative, 1992; nam_apap205-5_6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Administrative, 1993; nam_apap205-5_7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Administrative, 1995; nam_apap205-5_8 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Administrative, 1996; nam_apap205-5_9 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Administrative, 1996; nam_apap205-5_10 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Administrative, 1997; nam_apap205-5_11 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Administrative, 1997; nam_apap205-5_12 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Administrative, 1997; nam_apap205-5_13 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Administrative, 1998; nam_apap205-5_14 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Administrative, 1998; nam_apap205-5_15 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Administrative, 1998; nam_apap205-5_16 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Administrative, 1999; nam_apap205-5_17 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Annual Conference, 1990; nam_apap205-5_18 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Annual Conference, 1991; nam_apap205-5_19 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Annual Conference, 1992; nam_apap205-5_20 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Annual Conference, 1993; nam_apap205-5_21 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Annual Conference, 1994; nam_apap205-5_22 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Annual Conference, 1995; nam_apap205-5_23 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Annual Conference, 1996; nam_apap205-5_24 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Annual Conference, 1997; nam_apap205-5_25 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Annual Conference, 1998; nam_apap205-5_26 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Annual Conference, 1999; nam_apap205-5_27 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Bumper Sticker, Undated; nam_apap205-5_28 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Case Statement, 1991; nam_apap205-5_29 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 1988; nam_apap205-5_30 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 1990; nam_apap205-5_31 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, 1991; nam_apap205-5_32 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, 1992; nam_apap205-5_33 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, 1993; nam_apap205-5_34 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, 1994; nam_apap205-5_35 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, 1995; nam_apap205-5_36 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, 1996; nam_apap205-5_37 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, 1997; nam_apap205-5_38 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, 1998; nam_apap205-5_39 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, 1999; nam_apap205-5_40 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, Undated; nam_apap205-5_41 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - The Death Penalty: The Religious Community Calls for Abolition, Undated; nam_apap205-5_42 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Declaration of Life, 1997; nam_apap205-5_43 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Execution Statistics, 1990-1991; 1993-1994; nam_apap205-5_44 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Facing an Execution Guidelines, Undated; nam_apap205-5_45 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - General, 1988; 1991-1992; 1994; 1997; Undated; nam_apap205-5_46 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - " Human Rights and Human Wrongs " - report, 1997; nam_apap205-5_47 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - LifeLines, May-October, 1990; nam_apap205-5_48 (Oversize 8, Folder 4)
  - LifeLines, April-December, 1991; nam_apap205-5_49 (Oversize 8, Folder 5)
  - LifeLines, 1992; nam_apap205-5_50 (Oversize 8, Folder 6)
  - LifeLines, 1993; nam_apap205-5_51 (Oversize 8, Folder 7)
  - LifeLines, 1994; nam_apap205-5_52 (Oversize 8, Folder 8)
  - LifeLines, January-June, 1995; nam_apap205-5_53 (Oversize 8, Folder 9)
  - LifeLines, 1996; nam_apap205-5_54 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - LifeLines, 1997; nam_apap205-5_55 (Oversize 8, Folder 10)
  - LifeLines, May-June, 1998; nam_apap205-5_56 (Oversize 8, Folder 11)
  - LifeLines, November-December, 1998; nam_apap205-5_57 (Oversize 8, Folder 12)
  - Members Mailing Stickers, Undated; nam_apap205-5_58 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Midwest Regional Conference, 1990; 1992; nam_apap205-5_59 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - National Execution Alert, 1992-1993; nam_apap205-5_60 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - National Execution Alert, 1996; nam_apap205-5_61 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - National Execution Alert, 1997; nam_apap205-5_62 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - National Execution Alert, 1998; nam_apap205-5_63 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - National Execution Alert, 1999; nam_apap205-5_64 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - National Perspectives Portfolio, 1992; nam_apap205-5_65 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - " Nothing Cheap and Soothing about Multiple Executions " - Steven Hawkins and Donald Cabana, Undated; nam_apap205-5_66 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Pamphlets and Brochures, 1989; 1997; Undated; nam_apap205-5_67 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - " Public Opinion and the Death Penalty "- report, 1991; nam_apap205-5_68 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - State Reports, 1990-1991; nam_apap205-5_69 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Stop It! Campaign, 1991-1992; nam_apap205-5_70 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Thomas Thompson Case, 1997; nam_apap205-5_71 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- General Activism, 1984-2000, Undated; nam_apap205-6; 5.08 cubic feet
  This series contains records pertaining to various international, national, regional, state, and local activist organizations, non-profit groups, political parties, and religious organizations concerned with the death penalty and other activism related activities and events. The groups represented are primarily, but not exclusively, concerned with the abolition of the death penalty and prisoner rights. Included in this series are newsletters, correspondence, pamphlets, flyers, mass mailings, as well as a small amount of administrative material for organizations in which Bill Pelke himself was involved, such as the Indiana Coalition Against the Death Penalty (ICADP), the Northwest Indiana Coalition to the Abolish Control Unit Prisons, and the Northern Indiana Coalition Against the Death Penalty. Researchers should be aware that the bulk of this material consists of public outreach materials collected by Bill Pelke.
  - Abolition: Death Penalty News in Mississippi, 1996-1997; nam_apap205-6_1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abolitionist Action Committee, 1994-1995; 1997-1998; Undated; nam_apap205-6_2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abolitionist Action Committee - Fast and Vigil, 1995-1998; nam_apap205-6_3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abolitionist Action Committee Packet, 1997; nam_apap205-6_4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ACLU, 1984; 1995-1996; nam_apap205-6_5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - ACLU, Undated; nam_apap205-6_6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - ACLU Abolitionist, 1995; nam_apap205-6_7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - ACLU Abolitionist, 1995; nam_apap205-6_8 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - ACLU Abolitionist, 1996; nam_apap205-6_9 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - ACLU Abolitionist, 1996; nam_apap205-6_10 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ACLU Abolitionist, 1996; nam_apap205-6_11 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ACLU Abolitionist, 1997; nam_apap205-6_12 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - ACLU -Race and the Death Penalty: Georgia and the Nation, 1987; nam_apap205-6_13 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Activism - Brochures and Pamphlets, Undated; nam_apap205-6_14 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Activism - Events, 1989; 1991-1994; nam_apap205-6_15 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Activism - Events, 1995-1998; nam_apap205-6_16 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Activism - Events, Undated; nam_apap205-6_17 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Activism - General, 1989-1991; nam_apap205-6_18 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Activism - General, 1992-1993; nam_apap205-6_19 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Activism - General, 1994-1995; nam_apap205-6_20 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Activism - General, 1996-1997; nam_apap205-6_21 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Activism - General, 1998-1999; nam_apap205-6_22 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Activism - General, Undated; nam_apap205-6_23 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Activism - General, Undated; nam_apap205-6_24 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Activism - General, Undated; nam_apap205-6_25 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Activism Merchandise, 1995; 1997-1998; Undated; nam_apap205-6_26 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Activism - Petitions, 1993; Undated; nam_apap205-6_27 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Activism - Miscellaneous Newsletters, 1992-1993; 1995; 1997-1998; Undated; nam_apap205-6_28 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Activism - Pleas for Help, 1993-1999; Undated; nam_apap205-6_29 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Activism - Pleas for Help, 1993-1999; Undated; nam_apap205-6_30 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Activism - Sample / Model Letters, 1991; 1993; 1996-1997; Undated; nam_apap205-6_31 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Alabama Committee to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1992-1993; 1995; Undated; nam_apap205-6_32 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Alabama Prison Project, 1990; 1996-1997; nam_apap205-6_33 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Alternatives to Violence Project, Undated; nam_apap205-6_34 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - American Bar Association - Death Penalty Representation Project Packet, 2000; nam_apap205-6_35 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - American Friends Service Committee, 1998; Undated; nam_apap205-6_36 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - American Friends Service Committee -Forging Justice, 1990; nam_apap205-6_37 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - American Friends Service Committee -Forging Justice, 1991; nam_apap205-6_38 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - American Friends Service Committee - Religious Organizing Against the Death Penalty, 1997-1998; nam_apap205-6_39 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - American Friends Service Committee - Religious Organizing Against the Death Penalty - project packet, Undated; nam_apap205-6_40 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - The Andrew Lee Jones Fund, 1995; Undated; nam_apap205-6_41 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Baton Rouge Catholic Worker, 1997; nam_apap205-6_42 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Baton Rouge Catholic Worker, 1998; nam_apap205-6_43 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Baton Rouge Catholic Worker, 1998; nam_apap205-6_44 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Baton Rouge Catholic Worker, 1999; nam_apap205-6_45 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Blueprint for Social Justice, 1991; nam_apap205-6_46 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Bill Pelke - Activism, 1989-1991; nam_apap205-6_47 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Bruderhof Communities - Children's Crusade, 1997; nam_apap205-6_48 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Bruderhof Communities -The Plough, 1996; nam_apap205-6_49 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Bruderhof Communities -The Plough, 1997; nam_apap205-6_50 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Bruderhof Communities -The Plough, 1998; nam_apap205-6_51 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Bruderhof Communities -The Plough, 1999; nam_apap205-6_52 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Bruderhof Communities - Plough Books Catalogs, 1997-1998; Undated; nam_apap205-6_53 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Bruderhof Communities - Plough Books Online, 1997; nam_apap205-6_54 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Bruderhof Communities - Plough Publishing, Undated; nam_apap205-6_55 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Bruderhof Communities - Just-Us: Voices for Life, 1996; nam_apap205-6_56 (Oversize 9, Cd 1)
  - Bruderhof Communities - Take My Hand, 1997; nam_apap205-6_57 (Oversize 9, Cassette 1)
  - CACJ / CPDA Capital Defense Seminar, 1996-1997; nam_apap205-6_58 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Call to Action, 1995-1996; 1998; nam_apap205-6_59 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Catholics Against Capital Punishment, 1994; 1997; Undated; nam_apap205-6_60 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Center for Community Justice, 1993; Undated; nam_apap205-6_61 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - The Center for the Homeless, Inc., 1992-1993; nam_apap205-6_62 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - The Cesar Chavez Catholic Worker House, 1994; 1996; nam_apap205-6_63 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Cesar Chavez Community House, 1995-1997; nam_apap205-6_64 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Cesar Chavez Foundation, 1994-1996; Undated; nam_apap205-6_65 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Cesar Chavez Foundation, 1994-1996; Undated; nam_apap205-6_66 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Citizens United for Aleternatives to the Death Penalty, 1997-1998; Undated; nam_apap205-6_67 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Penalty (CUADP) - Button, Undated; nam_apap205-6_68 (Oversize 5, Item 10)
  - Coalition Against Indiana Control Units and Prison Abuse, 1994; nam_apap205-6_69 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1992; nam_apap205-6_70 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1993; nam_apap205-6_71 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1994; nam_apap205-6_72 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1995; nam_apap205-6_73 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1995; nam_apap205-6_74 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1996; nam_apap205-6_75 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1997; nam_apap205-6_76 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1998; nam_apap205-6_77 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1998; nam_apap205-6_78 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1998; nam_apap205-6_79 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1998; nam_apap205-6_80 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1999; nam_apap205-6_81 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 1999; nam_apap205-6_82 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Coalition for Prisoners' Rights Newsletter, 2000; nam_apap205-6_83 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Coalition of Arizonans to Abolish the Death Penalty -CAADP News, 1996-1997; nam_apap205-6_84 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Coalition to Defeat SR - 395, 1994; nam_apap205-6_85 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Committee for Freedom -Human Rights Held Hostage, 1993; nam_apap205-6_86 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Committee to End the Marion Lockdown, 1993-1995; 1997-1998; Undated; nam_apap205-6_87 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Committee to End the Marion Lockdown -Walkin' Steel, 1992; nam_apap205-6_88 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Committee to End the Marion Lockdown -Walkin' Steel, 1993; nam_apap205-6_89 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Committee to End the Marion Lockdown -Walkin' Steel, 1995; nam_apap205-6_90 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Committee to End the Marion Lockdown -Walkin' Steel, 1998; nam_apap205-6_91 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Committee to Stop Execution, Undated; nam_apap205-6_92 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Conneticut Network to Abolish the Death Penallty -Network News, 1994; nam_apap205-6_93 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Covenant House, Undated; nam_apap205-6_94 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Crime Victime Services -Victim Watch, 1994; nam_apap205-6_95 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Crime Victime Services -Victim Watch, 1994-1995; nam_apap205-6_96 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Crime Victime Services -Victim Watch, 1996; nam_apap205-6_97 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Crime Victime Services -Victim Watch, 1996-1997; nam_apap205-6_98 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Crime Victime Services -Victim Watch, 1997; nam_apap205-6_99 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Criminal Justice and Prison Ministry Conference Packet, 1997; nam_apap205-6_100 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Criminal Justice Newsletter, 1990; nam_apap205-6_101 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - CURE - Indiana Chapter, 1991-1993; 1995-1996; Undated; nam_apap205-6_102 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - CURE - OhioChapter, 1992; nam_apap205-6_103 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Death Penalty Focus of California, 1994-1999; nam_apap205-6_104 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Death Penalty Focus of California -The Sentry, 1991-1992; nam_apap205-6_105 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Death Penalty Focus of California -The Sentry, 1993-1994; nam_apap205-6_106 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Death Penalty Focus of California -The Sentry, 1995-1996; nam_apap205-6_107 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Death Penalty Focus of California -The Sentry, 1997-1998; nam_apap205-6_108 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Death Penalty Focus of California -The Sentry, 2000; nam_apap205-6_109 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Death Penalty Information Center, 1992-1994; 1996-1997; Undated; nam_apap205-6_110 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Death Penalty Information Center - reports, 1992-1994; 1996; nam_apap205-6_111 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - The Death Row Forum, 1996; Undated; nam_apap205-6_112 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1994; nam_apap205-6_113 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1994; nam_apap205-6_114 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1995; nam_apap205-6_115 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1995; nam_apap205-6_116 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1995; nam_apap205-6_117 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1996; nam_apap205-6_118 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1996; nam_apap205-6_119 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1996; nam_apap205-6_120 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1996; nam_apap205-6_121 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1997; nam_apap205-6_122 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1997; nam_apap205-6_123 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1998; nam_apap205-6_124 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1998; nam_apap205-6_125 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1998; nam_apap205-6_126 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - The Death Row Forum - newsletters, 1999; nam_apap205-6_127 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Death Row's Lamp, 1998; nam_apap205-6_128 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Dismas of Michiana, 1994-1995; 1997-1998; Undated; nam_apap205-6_129 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Dismas News, 1993-1995; 1997-1998; nam_apap205-6_130 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Double Justice: Race and Capital Punishment, 1993; nam_apap205-6_131 (Oversize 9, Vhs 3)
  - Emerging Summit to Strategize for the Abolition of the Death Penalty, 1997; nam_apap205-6_132 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Endeavor: Live Voices from Death Row Across the U.S.A., 1990-1991; nam_apap205-6_133 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Endeavor: Live Voices from Death Row Across the U.S.A., 1993; nam_apap205-6_134 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Endeavor: Live Voices from Death Row Across the U.S.A., 1994-1996; nam_apap205-6_135 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Endeavor Project, 1992; Undated; nam_apap205-6_136 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Envisioning a World Without Violence Conference, Undated; nam_apap205-6_137 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Execute Justice Not People - Button, Undated; nam_apap205-6_138 (Oversize 5, Item 12)
  - Fifth Avenue Foundation, 1994-196; Undated; nam_apap205-6_139 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Florida Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1991-1993; 1997; Undated; nam_apap205-6_140 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Forgiveness Institute, 1997; nam_apap205-6_141 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Free Carl Napier - Bumper Sticker, Undated; nam_apap205-6_142 (Oversize 5, Item 65)
  - Friends Committee to Abolish the Death Penalty -The Quaker Abolitionist, 1996; nam_apap205-6_143 (Box 2, Folder 66)